

# N ATALIJA N IKOLIĆ

### VISUAL ARTIST

Professional Visual Artist with experience in the VFX industry, dedicated to producing compelling visuals for film, television, and commercials. Bringing a fresh perspective to projects, combining technical expertise with a passion for storytelling to create immersive visual experiences.

# **CONTACT**

Email:

nikolic.natalija7@gmail.com

Website:

https://natalija-nikolic98.github.io/

# **SKILLS**

- Creative
- Innovative
- Team player
- Communicative
- Adaptive
- Detail-oriented
- Research

# **SOFTWARE**

- Unreal Engine
- Autodesk Maya
- ZBrush
- Pftrack
- Adobe Substance Painter
- Premiere Pro
- After Effects

## **EDUCATION**

#### THE COLLEGE OF FINE AND APPLIED ARTS

2017 - 2020

Bachelor's Degree - Image Media

2020 - 2023

Master's Degree - Audio Visual Composition

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## FREELANCE - DIGITAL ARTIST

2019 - present

- 2D Illustrations
- Video Editing

## **QLBEANS - MATCHMOVE AND LAYOUT ARTIST**

2021 - Present

- Matchmove and Layout
- · 3D Modeling and Sculpting

# **CERTIFICATION AND PROGRAMS**

Unreal Fellowship: Storytelling

Serbian Games Association: Playing Narratives

**Crater Training Centar: Unreal Engine Essentials**